Guide to the Argus Archives Records
Argus Archives Records
- The Animals' Agenda, 1979-2002; 1979 2002; 50 linear feet
  - The Humane Society of the United States, Washington D.C. (HSUS): AA23 - Directory of HSUS employees, 1997 July (Box 2.049, Folder 4)
  - The Humane Society of the United States, Washington D.C. (HSUS): AA24 - Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 2.049, Folder 5)
  - The Humane Society of the United States, Washington D.C. (HSUS): AA25 - Information kit relating to dissection, 1997 (Box 2.049, Folder 6)
  - The Humane Society of the United States, Washington D.C. (HSUS): AA26 - Published articles, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.049, Folder 7)
  - The Humane Society of the United States, Washington D.C. (HSUS): AA27 - Newsletters, 1990s (Box 2.049, Folder 8)
  - The Humane Society of the United States, Washington D.C. (HSUS): AA28 - Newsletters, 1990s (Box 2.049, Folder 9)
  - The Humane Society of the United States, Washington D.C. (HSUS): AA29 - Annual report, and status of pending federal legislation of the 104th congress, 1995 December, 1998 (Box 2.049, Folder 10)
  - The Humane Society of the United States, Washington D.C. (HSUS): AA30 - Guide relating to cat care, AA31 - Report on Factory Farming, folder empty, 1990s (Box 2.049, Folder 11)
  - The Humane Society of the United States, Washington D.C. (HSUS): AA32 - Report relating to the use of dog and cat fur, 1997 (Box 2.049, Folder 12)
  - The Humane Society of the United States, Washington D.C. (HSUS): AA33 - New-clippings, 1990s (Box 2.049, Folder 13)
  - The Humane Society of the United States, Washington D.C. (HSUS): AA34 - 103rd Congress; AAA Congressional Scorecard, 1994-1995 (Box 2.049, Folder 14)
  - The Humane Society of the United States, Washington D.C. (HSUS): AA35 - Publication, "Student Action Guide,", 1990s (Box 2.049, Folder 15)
  - The Humane Society of the United States, Washington D.C. (HSUS): AA36 - Booklet, "Celebrating the Humane Spirit," A tribute to John A. Hoyt, 1997 (Box 2.049, Folder 16)
  - The Humane Society of the United States, Washington D.C. (HSUS): AA37 - Report relating to animal sexual abuse, 1998 February (Box 2.049, Folder 17)
  - The Humane Society of the United States, Washington D.C. (HSUS): AA38 - Transcripts of testimonies, AA39 - Legislative reference guide, folder empty, 1993-1994 (Box 2.049, Folder 18)
  - The Humane Society of the United States, Washington D.C. (HSUS): AA40 - Memorandum. U.S. House of Representatives Committee on Resources, 1997 July 19 (Box 2.049, Folder 19)
  - The Humane Society of the United States, Washington D.C. (HSUS): AA41 - Media kits, 1990s (Box 2.049, Folder 20)
  - The Humane Society / SPCA of Austin and Travis County, Austin TX:AA1 - Bulletins, 1997-1999 (Box 2.05, Folder 1)
  - The Humane Society of Utah, Salt Lake City, UT (HSU): AA1 - Bulletins, 1993 October 4 (Box 2.05, Folder 2)
  - Humane Society of Sumner County, Hendersonville TN (HSSC): AA1 - Newsletter, 1998 Spring (Box 2.05, Folder 3)
  - Humane Society of Western Australia, Inc: AA1 - Correspondence, 1995 March 23 (Box 2.05, Folder 4)
  - Humane Society of Willamette Valley, Salem OR (HSWV): AA1 - Bulletin, 1996 August 1 (Box 2.05, Folder 5)
  - Humanitarians For Environmental and Animal Laws PAC. Lansing, MI (HEAL-PAC): AA1 - Bulletins, 1990s (Box 2.05, Folder 6)
  - Humanitarians For Environmental and Animal Laws PAC. Lansing, MI (HEAL-PAC): AA2 - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 2.05, Folder 7)
  - Humboldt Wildlife Care Center, Eureka, CA: AA1 - Published article, 1992 February 16 (Box 2.05, Folder 8)
  - The IAMS Company, Dayton, Ohio: AA1 - Printed matter, 1999 (Box 2.05, Folder 9)
  - Iberian Wolf Recovery Center, Malveira, Portugal: AA1 - Newsletters, 1995 (Box 2.05, Folder 10)
  - I Care: AA1 - Printed matter, 1990s (Box 2.05, Folder 11)
  - Idaho Animal Advocates, Sun Valley, ID (IAA): AA1 - Printed matter, 1995 (Box 2.05, Folder 12)
  - Idaho Coalition United For Bears (I-CUB): AA1 - Printed matter, 1995 (Box 2.05, Folder 13)
  - Idaho Department of Fish and Game (IDFG): AA1 - Published articles, 1998 May 31 (Box 2.05, Folder 14)
  - Illinois Animal Action, Inc., Warrenville IL (IAA): AA1 - Pamphlets, 1998-1999 (Box 2.05, Folder 15)
  - Illinois Animal Action, Inc., Warrenville IL (IAA): AA2 - Newsletters, 1997-1999 (Box 2.05, Folder 16)
  - Illinois Animal Action, Inc., Warrenville IL (IAA): AA3 - Press releases, 1990s (Box 2.05, Folder 17)
  - Illinois Animal Action, Inc., Warrenville IL (IAA): AA4 - News clippings, 1999 (Box 2.05, Folder 18)
  - Illinois Citizens' Animal Welfare League, Chicago IL (ICAWL): AA1 - Newsletters, 1991-1994 (Box 2.05, Folder 19)
  - Illinois Citizens' Animal Welfare League, Chicago IL (ICAWL): AA2 - Program, 1992 April 24 (Box 2.05, Folder 20)
  - Illinois Citizens for Humane Legislation, Chicago, IL (ICHL): AA1 - Newsletters, 1989, 1991 (Box 2.05, Folder 21)
  - In Defense of Animals, San Rafael, CA (IDA): AA1 - Pamphlets, 1990s (Box 2.05, Folder 22)
  - In Defense of Animals, San Rafael, CA (IDA): AA2 - Bulletins, 1990s (Box 2.051, Folder 1)
  - In Defense of Animals, San Rafael, CA (IDA): AA3 - Newsletters, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.051, Folder 2)
  - In Defense of Animals, San Rafael, CA (IDA): AA4 - Printed matter, 1990s (Box 2.051, Folder 3)
  - In Defense of Animals, San Rafael, CA (IDA): AA5 - Printed matter, 1990s (Box 2.051, Folder 4)
  - In Defense of Animals, San Rafael, CA (IDA): AA6 - Press releases, 1990s-2000 (Box 2.051, Folder 5)
  - In Defense of Animals, San Rafael, CA (IDA): AA7 - Publications, 1989-1990s (Box 2.051, Folder 6)
  - In Defense of Animals, San Rafael, CA (IDA): AA8 - Correspondence, 1990s (Box 2.051, Folder 7)
  - In Defense of Animals, San Rafael, CA (IDA): AA9 - Published articles, 1990s (Box 2.051, Folder 8)
  - In Defense of Animals, San Rafael, CA (IDA): AA10 - News clippings, 1989-1990s (Box 2.051, Folder 9)
  - In Defense of Animals, San Rafael, CA (IDA): AA11 - Reports relating to military use of animals, 1994 (Box 2.051, Folder 10)
  - In Defense of Animals, San Rafael, CA (IDA): AA12 - Transcripts of testimony, 1992, 1994 (Box 2.051, Folder 11)
  - In Defense of Animals, San Rafael, CA (IDA): AA13 - Report relating to animal research facilities, 1990s (Box 2.052, Folder 1)
  - In Defense of Animals, San Rafael, CA (IDA): AA14 - Statistical report, 1994 June 24 (Box 2.052, Folder 2)
  - In Defense of Animals, San Rafael, CA (IDA): AA15 - Complaint to the United States Department of Agriculture, 1993 August 16 (Box 2.052, Folder 3)
  - In Defense of Animals, San Rafael, CA (IDA): AA16 - Injunction order, 1992 November 4 (Box 2.052, Folder 4)
  - In Defense of Animals, San Rafael, CA (IDA): AA17 - Field report, 1994 (Box 2.052, Folder 5)
  - In Defense of Animals, San Rafael, CA (IDA): AA18 - Printed matter, media kit, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.052, Folder 6)
  - In Defense of Animals, San Rafael, CA (IDA): AA19 - Petition, 1993 November 18 (Box 2.052, Folder 7)
  - Independent Press Association (IPA):AA1 - Newsletters, 1998-1999 (Box 2.052, Folder 8)
  - Independent Citizens Research Foundation for the Study of Degenerative Diseases, Inc., (ICRF): AA1 - Newsletter, 1992 (Box 2.052, Folder 9)
  - Indiana Vegetarian Community: AA1 - Bulletins, 1998 (Box 2.052, Folder 10)
  - Incurably Ill For Animal Research (iiFOR): AA1 - Pamphlets, 1992 (Box 2.052, Folder 11)
  - Incurably Ill For Animal Research (iiFOR): AA2 - Correspondence, 1996 August 15 (Box 2.052, Folder 12)
  - Incurably Ill For Animal Research (iiFOR): AA3 - Newsletters, 1995-1996 (Box 2.052, Folder 13)
  - Incurably Ill For Animal Research (iiFOR): AA4 - Published articles, 1988-1989 (Box 2.052, Folder 14)
  - Incurably Ill For Animal Research (iiFOR): AA5 - Printed matter, 1980s (Box 2.052, Folder 15)
  - Inherit the Earth:Cranfordsville, IN: AA1 - Correspondence, circa 1992 (Box 2.052, Folder 16)
  - Inherit the Earth:Cranfordsville, IN: AA2 - Newsletter, 1996 May (Box 2.052, Folder 17)
  - Inherit the Earth:Cranfordsville, IN: AA3 - News clippings, 1996 (Box 2.052, Folder 18)
  - Institute for Captive Chimpanzee Care (ICCC): AA1 - Pamphlet, 1998 (Box 2.052, Folder 19)
  - The Institute for consumer Responsibility, Seattle, WA (NBN): AA1 - Publications, National Boycott News, 1992-1993 (Box 2.052, Folder 20)
  - The Institute for consumer Responsibility, Seattle, WA (NBN): AA2 - Correspondence, 1992 November 2 (Box 2.052, Folder 21)
  - The Institute for Earth Education, Greenville, WV: AA1 - Press releases, 1993 (Box 2.052, Folder 22)
  - The Institute for Food and Development Policy, San Francisco, CA: AA1 - Pamphlet, 1990s (Box 2.052, Folder 23)
  - The Institute for Food and Development Policy, San Francisco, CA: AA1 - Publications, 1982, 1990 (Box 2.052, Folder 24)
  - Institute for Public Affairs: AA1 - Magazine In These Times, 1999 June 13 (Box 2.052, Folder 25)
  - Institute for Scientific Information, Philadelphia, PA (ISI): AA1 - Printed matter, 1994 (Box 2.052, Folder 26)
  - Interagency Goat Management Team, Port Angeles, WA (IGMT): AA1 - Newsletter, 1992 June (Box 2.052, Folder 27)
  - International Association Against Painful Experiments on Animals, Hertfordshire, England (IAAPEA): AA1 - Pamphlets, 1989 (Box 2.052, Folder 28)
  - International Association Against Painful Experiments on Animals, Hertfordshire, England (IAAPEA): AA2 - Newsletters, 1992-1993 (Box 2.052, Folder 29)
  - International Association Against Painful Experiment on Animals, Hertfordshire, England (IAAPEA): AA3 - Printed matter, 1989-1992 (Box 2.052, Folder 30)
  - International Association Against Painful Experiments on Animals, Hertfordshire, England (IAAPEA): AA4 - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 2.052, Folder 31)
  - International Association Against Painful Experiments on Animals, Hertfordshire, England (IAAPEA): AA5 - Press release, 1992 August 12 (Box 2.052, Folder 32)
  - International Association of Human-Animal Interaction Organizations (IAHAIO):AA1 - Guidelines, Call for Papers, 1995 March 1 (Box 2.052, Folder 33)
  - International Berkeley Bird Rescue, Berkeley, CA (IBBR): SS1 - News clippings, 1990s (Box 2.052, Folder 34)
  - International Center for Technology Assessment (ICTA): AA1 - Bulletin, circa 1999 (Box 2.052, Folder 35)
  - International Defenders of Animals Inc., Hermitage, MO (IDA): AA1 - News clippings, 1970, 1998 (Box 2.052, Folder 36)
  - International Foundation for Ethical Research (IFER): AA1 - Pamphlets, 1989 (Box 2.052, Folder 37)
  - International Foundation for Ethical Research (IFER): AA2 - Printed matter, 1980s (Box 2.052, Folder 38)
  - International Foundation for Ethical Research (IFER): AA3 - Published article, 1980s (Box 2.052, Folder 39)
  - International Foundation for Ethical Research (IFER): AA4 - A Proposal to the Foundation, 1980s (Box 2.052, Folder 40)
  - International Foundation for Ethical Research (IFER): AA5 - Correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 2.052, Folder 41)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare, Yarmouth Port, MA (IFAW): AA1 - Pamphlets, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.053, Folder 1)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare, Yarmouth Port, MA (IFAW): AA2 - Printed matter, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.053, Folder 2)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare, Yarmouth Port, MA (IFAW): AA3 - Bulletins, 1990s (Box 2.053, Folder 3)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare, Yarmouth Port, MA (IFAW): AA4 - Bulletins, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.053, Folder 4)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare, Yarmouth Port, MA (IFAW): AA5 - Bulletins, 1980s (Box 2.053, Folder 5)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare, Yarmouth Port, MA (IFAW): AA6 - Printed matter, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.053, Folder 6)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare, Yarmouth Port, MA (IFAW): AA7 - Correspondence, 1977, 1981, 1997 (Box 2.053, Folder 7)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare, Yarmouth Port, MA (IFAW): AA8 - Annual reports, 1980, 1996 (Box 2.053, Folder 8)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare, Yarmouth Port, MA (IFAW): AA9 - Transcripts of radio programs, 1996 (Box 2.053, Folder 9)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare, Yarmouth Port, MA (IFAW): AA10 -Report " Canada's Seal hunt, 1996 (Box 2.053, Folder 10)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare, Yarmouth Port, MA (IFAW): AA11 - Brief on alternatives to animal testing - Report related to Seal hunting, 1994 July 20 (Box 2.053, Folder 11)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare, Yarmouth Port, MA (IFAW): AA12 - Report related to Seal hunting, 1998 April 20 (Box 2.053, Folder 12)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare, Yarmouth Port, MA (IFAW): AA13 - News clippings, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.053, Folder 13)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare, Yarmouth Port, MA (IFAW): AA14 - Published articles, 1997-1998 (Box 2.054, Folder 1)
  - International Generic Horse Association(IGHA)/ Horse Aid, Rancho Palos Verdes, CA: AA1 - Newsletters, 1996-1997 (Box 2.054, Folder 2)
  - International League for the Protection of Horses, Hamilton, New Zealand (ILPH): AA1 - Printed matter, 1990s (Box 2.054, Folder 4)
  - International Marine Mammal Project (IMMP): AA1 - Postcards, 1990s (Box 2.054, Folder 5)
  - International Monetary Fund (IMF): AA1 - News clippings, 1998 (Box 2.054, Folder 6)
  - International Network for Religion and Animals, Washington D.C. (INRA): AA1 - Pamphlets, 1990s (Box 2.054, Folder 7)
  - International Network for Religion and Animals, Washington D.C. (INRA): AA2 - Printed matter, 1990s (Box 2.054, Folder 8)
  - International Network for Religion and Animals, Washington D.C. (INRA): AA3 - Information packet relating to World Week of Prayer for Animals, 1990 August 30 (Box 2.054, Folder 9)
  - International Network for Religion and Animals, Washington D.C. (INRA): AA4 - Correspondence, 1990, 1991 (Box 2.054, Folder 10)
  - International Peace Forest, Gloucestershire, UK (IPF): AA1 - Newsletter, 1994 June (Box 2.054, Folder 11)
  - International Primate Protection League, Summerville, SC (IPPL): AA1 - Printed matter, 1990s (Box 2.054, Folder 12)
  - International Primate Protection League, Summerville, SC (IPPL): AA2 - Correspondence, 1990s (Box 2.054, Folder 13)
  - International Primate Protection League, Summerville, SC (IPPL): AA3 - Published articles, 1990s (Box 2.054, Folder 14)
  - International Primate Protection League, Summerville, SC (IPPL): AA4 - Legal record of information that may become testimony, 1991 June 17 (Box 2.054, Folder 15)
  - International Society for Animal rights, Inc., Clarks Summit, PA (ISAR): AA1 - Newsletters, 1970s-1990s (Box 2.054, Folder 16)
  - International Society for Animal rights, Inc., Clarks Summit, PA (ISAR): AA2 - Pamphlets, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.054, Folder 17)
  - International Society for Animal rights, Inc., Clarks Summit, PA (ISAR): AA3 - Printed matter, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.054, Folder 18)
  - International Society for Animal rights, Inc., Clarks Summit, PA (ISAR): AA4 - Correspondence, 1989-1990s (Box 2.054, Folder 19)
  - International Society for Animal rights, Inc., Clarks Summit, PA (ISAR): AA5 - Report, "Surplus Population: A Fallacious Basis for Sport Hunting,", 1979 (Box 2.054, Folder 20)
  - International Society for Animal rights, Inc., Clarks Summit, PA (ISAR): AA6 - Information kits, 1996, 1997 (Box 2.054, Folder 21)
  - International Society for Animal rights, Inc., Clarks Summit, PA (ISAR): AA8 - Bulletins, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.054, Folder 23)
  - International Society for the Protection of exotic Animal Kind and Livestock (ISPEAK): AA1 - Printed matter, 1996-1997 (Box 2.054, Folder 24)
  - International Society for the Protection of exotic Animal Kind and Livestock (ISPEAK): AA2 - Published articles, 1997 (Box 2.054, Folder 25)
  - International Society for Krishna Consciousness (ISKON): AA1 - Newsletters, 1992, 1999 (Box 2.054, Folder 26)
  - International Society for the Preservation of the Tropical Rainforest, Rosemead, CA: Bulletin, 1992 March 10 (Box 2.054, Folder 27)
  - International Society for the Protection of Mustangs and Burros (ISPMB): AA1 - bulletins, AA2 - correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 2.054, Folder 28)
  - International Wildlife Coalition, North Falmouth, MA (IWC): AA1 - Bulletins, 1990s (Box 2.054, Folder 29)
  - International Wildlife Coalition, North Falmouth, MA (IWC): AA2 - Printed matter, 1990s (Box 2.054, Folder 30)
  - International Wildlife Coalition, North Falmouth, MA (IWC): AA3 - Correspondence, 1990 August 22 (Box 2.054, Folder 31)
  - International Wildlife Coalition, North Falmouth, MA (IWC): AA4 - News clippings, 1985 January 15 (Box 2.054, Folder 32)
  - International Wildlife Coalition, North Falmouth, MA (IWC): AA4 - Newsletters, Children's Whalewatch, 1990, 1993 (Box 2.054, Folder 33)
  - International Wildlife Film Festival, Missoula, Montana: AA1 - press releases, 1998-1999 (Box 2.055, Folder 1)
  - International Wolf Center, Minneapolis, Minnesota: AA1 - publications, 1996-1999 (Box 2.055, Folder 2)
  - Interspecies Communication, Friday Harbor, Washington: AA1 - correspondence, AA2 - unpublished records, 1991-1997, undated (Box 2.055, Folder 3)
  - Inverted-A Horn, Grand Prairie, Texas: AA1 - publications, 1998 (Box 2.055, Folder 4)
  - Iowa Alliance for Animals, Ames, Iowa: AA1 - printed matter, 1992 (Box 2.055, Folder 5)
  - Iowa State University Press: AA1 - catalog, 1999 (Box 2.055, Folder 6)
  - Ipswich Equine Rescue Corporation: AA1 - newsletter, 1998 (Box 2.055, Folder 7)
  - Iron Frog Productions: AA1 - information kit, 1998 (Box 2.055, Folder 8)
  - Island Vegetarians, Lindenhurst, New York: AA1 - newsletters, 1990-1991 (Box 2.055, Folder 9)
  - Issue Action Publications, Inc.: AA1 - newsletters, 1994-1998 (Box 2.055, Folder 10)
  - James Cross Productions: AA1 - media kit, AA2 - correspondence, 1980-1998 (Box 2.055, Folder 11)
  - James River Humane Society: AA1 - grant proposal, 1998 (Box 2.055, Folder 12)
  - The Jane Goodall Institute for Wildlife Research, Education, and Conservation (JGI - Silver Spring, Maryland): AA1 - bulletins, 1994-1997, undated (Box 2.055, Folder 13)
  - The Jane Goodall Institute for Wildlife Research, Education, and Conservation (JGI - Silver Spring, Maryland): AA2 - newsletters, AA3 - correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 2.055, Folder 14)
  - Janna Publications, Knoxville, Tennessee: AA1 - newsletters, 1996-1997 (Box 2.055, Folder 15)
  - Japan Anti-Vivisection Association, Tokyo, Japan (JAVA): AA1 - bulletins, 1992-1995 (Box 2.055, Folder 16)
  - Japan Anti-Vivisection Association, Tokyo, Japan (JAVA): AA1 - bulletins, 1996-1998 (Box 2.055, Folder 17)
  - Japan Anti-Vivisection Association, Tokyo, Japan (JAVA): AA2 - printed matter, AA3 - newsletters, 1994-1996, undated (Box 2.055, Folder 18)
  - Japan Anti-Vivisection Association, Tokyo, Japan (JAVA): AA4 - correspondence, AA5 - published articles, AA6 - newspaper clippings, 1992-1997 (Box 2.055, Folder 19)
  - Japan Environment Monitor (JEM): AA1 - publications, 1988, 1991 (Box 2.055, Folder 20)
  - Jes Exotics Sanctuary, Sharon, Wisconsin: AA1 - pamphlet, AA2 - newsletters [and news clippings and notes], 1993-1995, undated (Box 2.055, Folder 21)
  - Jewish Vegetarians of North America (JVNA): AA1 - bulletins, 1998 (Box 2.056, Folder 1)
  - Jews for Animal Rights, Marblehead, Massachusetts (JAR): AA1 - printed matter, AA2 - reports, 1993-1998 (Box 2.056, Folder 2)
  - The JG Press: AA1 - magazines, 1998-1999 (Box 2.056, Folder 3)
  - J.N. Townsend Publishing: AA1 - catalog, 1998 (Box 2.056, Folder 4)
  - Jolene's Horse Rescue: AA1 - bulletins, 1999, undated (Box 2.056, Folder 5)
  - The Joseph E. Morgan Research Foundation, Ottawa, Ontario, Canada (JFMRF): AA1 - newsletter, 1993 (Box 2.056, Folder 6)
  - Journal of Applied Animal Welfare Science, New York, New York (JAAWS): AA1 - bulletins, 1995 (Box 2.056, Folder 7)
  - Journal of Applied Animal Welfare Science, New York, New York (JAAWS): AA2 - publication, 1997 (Box 2.056, Folder 8)
  - Journal of Applied Animal Welfare Science, New York, New York (JAAWS): AA2 - publication, 1998 (Box 2.056, Folder 9)
  - Johns Hopkins Center for Alternatives to Animal Testing (CAAT): AA1 - pamphlet, AA2 - bulletins, AA3 - programs, 1992-1995 (Box 2.056, Folder 10)
  - Justice for Animals, Inc., Raleigh, North Carolina (JFA): AA1 - printed matter, AA2 - newsletters, circa 1991-1998 (Box 2.056, Folder 11)
  - Katuah Journal, Lenoir, North Carolina: AA1 - newspaper, 1991-1992 (Box 2.056, Folder 12)
  - Katuah Journal, Lenoir, North Carolina: AA2 - bulletins, 1993 (Box 2.056, Folder 13)
  - Kennedy Institute of Ethics, Washington, D.C.: AA1 - bulletin, 1995 (Box 2.056, Folder 14)
  - Kent Action Against Live Exports (KALE): AA1 - leaflets, undated (Box 2.056, Folder 15)
  - Kentucky Coalition for Animal Protection, Inc. (KCAP): AA1 - opinion, 1988 (Box 2.056, Folder 16)
  - Kenya Wildlife Service: AA1 - published article, 1998 (Box 2.056, Folder 17)
  - Key Deer Protection Alliance: AA1 - newspaper clipping, 1998 (Box 2.056, Folder 18)
  - Kick it Over Collective, Toronto, Ontario, Canada (KIC): AA1 -magazines, 1992-1993 (Box 2.056, Folder 19)
  - Kimber (K1): AA1 - printed materials, 1986-1993 (Box 2.056, Folder 20)
  - The Kindness Club: AA1 - publications, 1989-1990 (Box 2.056, Folder 21)
  - Klamath Basin Audubon Society, Klamath Falls, Oregon: AA1 - bulletin, 1995 (Box 2.056, Folder 22)
  - Labour Animal Welfare Society: AA1 - magazine, circa 1998 (Box 2.056, Folder 23)
  - Labrador Retriever Rescue News, Concord, Massachusetts: AA1 - printed matter, AA2 - newsletters, 1993 (Box 2.056, Folder 24)
  - Last Chance for Animals, Los Angeles, California (LCA): AA1 - pamphlets, 1990s (Box 2.056, Folder 25)
  - Last Chance for Animals, Los Angeles, California (LCA): AA2 - postcards, 1990s (Box 2.057, Folder 1)
  - Last Chance for Animals, Los Angeles, California (LCA): AA3 - printed matter, 1990s (Box 2.057, Folder 2)
  - Last Chance for Animals, Los Angeles, California (LCA): AA4 - newsletters [Release and Fighting Chance], 1996-1999 (Box 2.057, Folder 3)
  - Last Chance for Animals, Los Angeles, California (LCA): AA4 - newsletters [LCA Activist Update], 1990-1995 (Box 2.057, Folder 4)
  - Last Chance for Animals, Los Angeles, California (LCA): AA4 - newsletters [LCA Update], 1995-1999 (Box 2.057, Folder 5)
  - Last Chance for Animals, Los Angeles, California (LCA): AA5 - media kit, 1995 (Box 2.057, Folder 6)
  - Last Chance for Animals, Los Angeles, California (LCA): AA6 - published articles, AA7 - report, AA8 - correspondence, 1992-1999 (Box 2.057, Folder 7)
  - Lakin, [Margo](L1): printed materials, 1997-2000 (Box 2.057, Folder 8)
  - Lakota Wolf Refuge: AA1 - published article, 1998 (Box 2.057, Folder 9)
  - Land Air Water, Eugene, Oregon (LAW): AA1 - newsletters, 1996-2000 (Box 2.057, Folder 10)
  - Land and Liberty International, London, England: AA1 - newsletters, 1993-1995 (Box 2.057, Folder 11)
  - The Land Institute, Salina, Kansas: AA1 - bulletin, AA2 -newsletters, 1991-1992 (Box 2.057, Folder 12)
  - La Plata Animal Welfare Society, Durango, Colorado (LAPAW): AA1 - advertisement, 1989 (Box 2.057, Folder 13)
  - Law (L1): magazine, undated (Box 2.057, Folder 14)
  - Last Hope Wildlife Fund, El Paso, Texas (LHWF): AA1 - correspondence, 1994 (Box 2.057, Folder 15)
  - The Last Post, Falls Village, Connecticut: AA1 - pamphlet, undated (Box 2.057, Folder 16)
  - The Latham Foundation, Alameda, California: AA1 - bulletins, AA2 - brochure, AA3 - catalogs, circa 1991-circa 1992 (Box 2.057, Folder 17)
  - Lawyers Committee for the Enforcement of Animal Protection Laws, Inc., New York, New York (LCEAPL): AA1 - newsletter, AA2 - minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 2.057, Folder 18)
  - Lazarian Society for Animals, Cocheton, New York (LSA): AA1 - bulletins, 1994 (Box 2.057, Folder 19)
  - League Against Cruel Sports, London, England (LACS): AA1 - media kit, circa 1995 (Box 2.058, Folder 1)
  - League Against Cruel Sports, London, England (LACS): AA2 - report relating to hunting, undated (Box 2.058, Folder 2)